All right, everybody. Good afternoon.
Thanks for being with us. Thanks to
James for carving out some time.
>> Really cool to to be sitting, you know,
to be standing up here obviously after a
win. [music] Um, but I was just really
proud to be their coach today.
>> We we won the game. You know, my first
game was a [music] dub, so that's
exciting for me.
>> D, let's go, baby. One thing I [music]
will say is I thought he competed his
tail off. I thought he was, you know,
getting us again in and out of the right
things and made a lot of good throws,
man. To get up, break what, three
tackles or whatever it was, two tackles
and shed some dude off.
>> No running in the I mean that that's an
unbelievable individual effort.
[cheering]
>> I just told coach uh give me the ball. I
go there, make a play and he got me the
ball and I just did what I had to do.
>> Touchdown
Travis Hunter. I mean, I turned around,
I heard the th you know, turn around.
The ball's on the ground.
Jackson,
I'm exhausted. So, that's the thing
about the NFL is it doesn't it doesn't
let up, you know? So, you can't you
can't stay [music] in the rearview
mirror thinking about the last one cuz
this one is is just as important. what a
oneweek response by Liam Cohen and the
Jacksonville
>> play, you know, as we played on Sunday.
Um there's, you know, a [music] new
standard now in terms of, okay, well,
that's what it looks like when we
prepare the way we did and got ourselves
in the mindset mentality [music] to go
play that way. Tough all season, we had
some big wins, we've had some tough
losses, and you just keep playing. And
uh this week, obviously, it's a big one.
That whole need fans to pack the place
out and be loud for us and get
advantage.
How do you does that continue to go when
maybe the respect starts to come which
might be where you are right now really
get it. So that's the beauty of it
Lawrence as he's getting hit. I couldn't
believe he even tried that.
>> Never going to play scared. I'm going to
continue to let it rip. And I think
that's why you know we we have a chance
at the end of the day is cuz you keep
playing.
>> I don't think I ever seen Trev like
this.
>> But do you feel like this is a win that
can change the narrative for your group?
>> We don't care.
>> Yeah. We really don't care about the
narrative.
>> This a small market team, man.
I just want to tell you congratulations
on your success, young man. You hold
your head up. All right, ladies and
gentlemen. Duvall, you the one. All
right.
>> We I think we're really really close as
a team. [music] I mean, you guys been in
the locker room. I think y'all kind of
see how we talk to each other. Like, you
know what I'm saying? Those are really,
really my brothers. You know what I'm
saying? We calling each other for
everything. We spend a lot of time with
each other. We do a lot of things
outside of the field [music] together.
And um I think as the weeks go and we're
challenged with different things, I
think we [music] continue to grow closer
and closer.